Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as masters.
These lethal abilities, dutifully
passed down through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Hikaru Gero of the Poison Clan
and his greatest challenge yet,
to get married.
No mama, lots of time.
Fun, fun, fun, you so
cool, no, blah, blah?
kill or kiss.
toxic.
Let's go!
Kill our kids!
Kill, kill our kids!
All right!
Hope you're ready!
Time for the test of
courage, but where to?
There to!
The old shrine, but safety first!
The path is dangerous
without any ghosties.
So we put a cute photo op halfway.
We'll be handing out selfie sticks,
one for every two people
so no one gets separated.
Don't forget the flash.
Onward, you brave souls!
Let's all make memories
we'll treasure forever!
Yeah!
Gato, this'll be your big chance.
Surely even you've heard of
the suspension bridge effect.
When you cross one, you mistake your heart
racing for liking whoever you're with.
It's the same for ghosts.
Okay.
Remember, mood is key. Got that?
If you don't start seizing
this kind of opportunity,
you're going to end up
single the rest of your life!
Why does Kinosaki seem so into this?
I asked for help getting
married, but still.
You!
I wanted to say thank you for
sticking with me and stuff.
You don't have to pretend
this isn't a total pain.
I know it would have made your job a
lot easier if instead of coming here,
I just stayed home.
It wouldn't have mattered.
There's only so many options in the
woods for your attacker to take.
But if you really want to do me a favor,
it would be for the best if you could
forget your worries and just enjoy the trip.
You get a limited number of
opportunities like this in life.
There's no need to waste this one
just because someone wants you dead.
Worrying about you is my job.
Mr. Kato.
Guess this is it.
Let's see now.
How does this thing work?
Leave the camera work to me.
Okay, smile.
In three, two, one!
Mr. Gato?
Where'd you go?
I don't know how, but we
must have gotten separated.
I have to find him.
There you are.
What's wrong?
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
Shiori.
Dad, but you're dead.
You're at a crossroads between life and
death as a sacrifice to Lord Cladney.
Who'd have thought I'd end up getting a
chance to drink with my precious daughter?
Please, father. You told me.
Why did you pick me to
take over the company?
You're right.
What was I thinking?
I shouldn't have placed so much trust
in you just because you're my daughter.
Yes, it was my worst mistake.
But you already knew that, didn't you?
Attempting something beyond your limits
will only lead to one thing, Shiori.
Suffering.
The truth is you're never going to
be strong accept it and just let go.
I know you have expectations to live up to
mine and everyone else's
must be hard on you!
I just want to let go.
and not worry.
You're right.
It is exhausting.
But who cares?
Because it's all worth it!
I felt so alive when they
enjoyed my magic show!
Maybe I'll never be strong.
No matter how hard I push
myself, and even if I'm not?
I won't take the easy way out!
I'm done being afraid!
That's a long way down!
I'm going to die!
What should I do?
What's happening?
The rubber's too shallow!
Broke my pants!
Friends!
Umbrella?
Do your thing, umbrella!
If I die like this, I'll be letting
down everyone who's ever protected me!
I've got to do something!
But what?
I'm alive!
It's a miracle!
It's water-absorbent polymers!
They needed to make it look
like a suicide or accident.
Otherwise,
your relatives would be
suspects and could end
up losing a lot more
than their inheritance.
Everything down to the last
detail was planned out.
Even the legend of Lord
Cladney, all of it made up.
Right, Soundmaster Naruko?
That was a clever trick.
The moment she took that
picture at the photo op.
Mr.
Gale, where'd you go?
While I was distracted,
you hit me with a shockwave and
scrambled my sense of direction.
Separating me from Muresh, you know.
You're a lot feistier
than I thought you'd be.
I will super enjoy this.
Relax!
Like you said, suicide or accident,
I only dance the way they pay me to.
We're leaving.
It's too risky staying here.
On your feet.
I can't stand.
My knees gave up.
Well, if you can't run,
better hop on my back.
Thanks for preparing
me for this, Kinosaki.
I showed him the ropes.
Not what I had in mind, but sure.
We'll make it work.
Whatever you do, don't
let go of me. Right.
Modified Bloodline Plus Plus.
Mind Whisper.
What's going on?
If I had to guess, he's
messing with our minds.
Physical condition for Tissimo.
So this is the secret modified
bloodline of the Poison Masters.
Experiencing your toxic
vibes is a super rare treat.
I'm honored.
But, my mind whispers can reach
you anywhere on this mountain.
Escape is super impossible.
Ureshino, take these earplugs!
Wait, I think I practiced
a thing for this!
Kitty, you're noise-canceling headphones!
We can pair them and talk to each other.
They look great on you.
Mia, blocking your ears
isn't going to save you.
When my mind whispers stack together,
the blades have sound cut
right down to the bone.
Don't you feel embarrassed?
If I can't hear the attacks,
then I'll feel them.
I'll max out my strength, as well
as sharpen my tactile senses.
Toxin! Lunar Peak!
Those were smooth moves.
They won't save my target, though.
Ureshino, what?
I should have known.
Those attacks weren't meant for me.
He hid her headphones with the vibrations.
Just as I expected.
It's not only her father.
This girl, she's a
treasure trove of trauma.
There's so much material to work with,
I can keep breaking her
will over and over again.
What do you see?
Uncle?
I don't have to tell you
how I really feel, do I?
You've been nothing but a burden to me.
A pain.
I've had to do all the work
and deal with the shareholders.
It's exhausting.
Why do you think your uncle
let you go on this little trip?
He got on board with the
plan to wipe you out. Sad.
There's no one on your side.
That's nothing but a bunch of bull!
Before he chose me,
your uncle interviewed a ton of
bodyguards looking for a professional.
But he kept hiring scumbags who
had zero clue what they were doing.
He wound up shelling out a fortune
for every contract he had to cancel.
The only reason he reached out to me was
because of a Kray's 10,000-word review.
He trusted you'd be safe in my hands.
Would he have gone through all this
trouble if he didn't care about you?
Yurei!
I'm sorry, Ureshino, but
I need you to take a nap.
Hmm...
I'm dealing with a poison master.
Obviously he would be able to
navigate around my illusions.
You can hear me, can't you?
I know your illusions and
brainwashing tricks drag out traumatic
memories from deep within a person's
subconscious and amplify them.
Yes, she has a messy situation at home.
And yes, her uncle did give
her permission to go camping.
But that's only a small
part of the bigger picture.
He was tempted for a second to let her
go, and you amped up his urge to give in.
Ureshino knows she has weaknesses,
but she's fighting to overcome them.
So back off.
She doesn't need you
giving her a hard time.
Hmm well that's really
strange according to
my phone the two of them
should be right here
There you are wait a minute what the heck
So that's why you were running late
i'm glad i put a gps tracker on her
Courtesy of me kitami got a little work
related injury i pushed myself a bit
You're tracking me?
I need your help, Kinosaki.
Take Ureshino and get
away from this village.
Mm-hmm. I... what?
In order to complete his mission,
he'll need to eliminate me first.
I've already spoiled his plans twice now.
I have to take him out for good.
The thing is, while I'm tied
up, I need you to keep her safe.
Yeah, as your marriage advisor,
that's outside my purview.
I can make an exception, though.
So selfless.
Okay, let's go.
Let me see your headphones.
Just as I thought.
He took a big risk
getting that close to her.
He planted this to enhance his
illusions and brainwashing.
As far as his abilities go, I
don't know the full extent of them.
This will be fun.
If you're not going to fight me
face to face, I'll drag you out.
I'm fine right here.
If I go after the target, I might
end up with a syringe in my back.
Super bad news.
I need to get that Poison Master out of my
hair that I can take
my time with Ureshino.
That's how this tune goes.
And I've never felt readier to play.
It's time to perform.
The finale.
He just got a lot more serious.
Toxic gases dissipate
in the great outdoors.
As for poison needles, they're essentially
useless unless you're able to locate me.
So what's your next move?
Let's see you use those tricks of yours.
Once I dissolve your wires!
It bounced off?
My strings vibrate at super high speeds.
There's no way for Liquid to bind to them.
Now the climax can finally begin!
Modified bloodline plus plus grand actor
It stopped.
Even the legs.
But why?
What did you do, Poison Master?
Cut the trees instead of the wires?
No, I would have sensed it if he did.
You didn't wither them with poison either.
Actually, they look healthier than ever.
Wait, don't tell me.
Nice friends you've got.
They seem to like my medicine.
Your technique's hard to tune.
That's its one weak point.
If the trees continue growing,
you can't play precise notes.
Show's over.
Fear is buried deep down inside
a person's psyche, waiting.
I've already sown the seeds.
All that's left for me to
do is to allow them to grow.
Where have you two been?
We've got a huge emergency.
Rock slide?
But that's the only way out of here.
Someone started feeling sick
during the Test of Courage.
We tried driving them to
the hospital, but, well...
These mountains are too
dangerous for amateurs.
Let's wait for rescue.
Wait, look over there!
Let's hear that fear.
It's the wrath of Lord Clotney!
I don't want to die!
A sacrifice must be made!
We need to follow the legend.
To appease Lord Glotney,
we must offer up a child.
We must determine who here
among us is the youngest.
Whoever has the latest birthday will
be sacrificed to halt his wrath.
New students, take out
your IDs so we can check.
September 27th.
February 4th.
October 10th.
May 5th.
March 20th.
I was born in March on the 31st.
At this point, if you think you can
stop the seeds of panic from growing,
you're dead wrong.
Grab her!
She's getting away!
It's only a matter of time
until the target dies.
They'll never stop pursuing her.
That is, unless you're able to defeat me.
Super complete.
A violin?
He's gonna hit me!
With the Soundmaster's
modified bloodline increments!
Ah!
Next time, together with me.